FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Spill, Pineapple, Host, February
How did I become
queen
All characters are fictitious
and the events shown are fiction.
AZALEA
Come on.
I can't believe that the great Jang Bong Hwan
This kind of thing is required to maintain life.
Life is so worthless, isn't it?
I was really motivated.
Can I become a local?
Steve Jobs or Thomas Edison?
No, I'm taking it low. We need someone great.
Savior of the human race.
In the queen's body sits something
that shouldn't be there.
Evil spirit.
The Queen is possessed by an evil spirit!
I can't leave you like this.
Go away forever.
Exactly, Carrier! Inventor of air conditioners!
Your Majesty!
Come to your senses, Your Majesty! Come on.
Episode 7: Mask
-Charge 100 joules.
-Move away.
Administer epinephrine. Charge for 150 joules.
-Charge 150 joules.
-Move away.
- Live up.
-I'm coming.
Isn't this the queen's servant?
And the royal doctor runs after her.
-What's happened?
-Her Majesty...
Your Majesty. It's dangerous!
God.
Your Majesty.
I've been thinking about it, I'm nagging you for your own good...
Your Majesty!
What happened here?
They have already left for the royal physician.
Your Majesty.
You can't die!
Don't leave me!
I won't nag you anymore.
Come to your senses, Your Majesty.
Do something!
Your Majesty!
Hanguk University Hospital, Jang Bong Hwan
-Charge 100 joules.
-Ready.
Move away.
150 joules, done.
-He's back.
-What is this?
How bright. What is he doing?
Pulse is normal. Pressure?
The pressure is also normal.
Hospital? Am I back?
Returned. The truth is back.
Jang Bong Hwan, you were dying.
I know.
I thought for the rest of my life
I will be locked in a woman's body.
How many days have passed?
Exactly. How many days did I lie?
The body is so heavy.
A week has passed.
Time passed just like in Joseon.
First, help me stand up.
He was unconscious for a week
now in a vegetative state.
What does it mean to be in a vegetative state?
Hey Dr. Lee, are you talking about me?
What a vegetative state, am I normal?
What are you talking about?
-Watch him.
-Yes.
Where are you going?
Come back! I'm fine!
Yes, I'm like a cucumber!
What? Can't anyone hear me?
I'm here. I'm back.
Jang Bong Hwan is back!
When will the doctor come?
Queen!
-Your Majesty!
My queen, wake up!
What the hell is going on here?
She suddenly jumped up
then she turned pale and fell.
How could she fall out of the blue?
Probably poisoned.
She could have been poisoned!
What?
This can't be true.
We carefully monitor our products
outsiders are not allowed to enter here,
and the queen didn’t eat anything here.
Then what was she doing here?
Did you cook?
Yes.
She could have gotten poison
tasting the dishes, Your Majesty.
There is no way to be sure of this.
Dummies.
I've always been afraid
that something like this will happen.
And finally it happened!
Was she poisoned?
I...
I'll examine her.
Don't hesitate.
Pulse
not like a living one.
What does it mean?
Vegetative state.
Vegetative state?
Man cannot move and is like a vegetable.
Her blood and chi energy
gathered in the upper body,
the spirit has left the body and she hardly breathes.
If the chi energy returns, she will survive. If not -
she will die.
What does it mean to die?
What can I do
what to do to save her?
You need to pour hibiscus decoction and calamus juice into her mouth.
Chief Eunuch.
Bring everything immediately!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Will the Queen last until then?
This is the problem.
Don't just stand there, do something!
Save our queen.
To do anything, you need to move it.
Let's go to the Daejojeon Hall.
Your Majesty.
Queen Mother.
It is necessary to expel the evil spirit from the queen's body.
You can't hesitate.
And how to do this?
We will place it around the Daejojeon Hall
frightening objects
and block the energy.
And then we will perform the ritual of expelling the spirit.
It's dangerous. Cannot be carried out
such a ritual in the palace.
If we get caught...
There is no point in holding the ceremony outside the palace.
In order for the ritual to be successful, perform it
necessary near the queen.
Live up.
Yes.
-Did you finish?
-Yes, everything is ready.
What's happened?
The patient had cardiac arrest.
Listen. Here. Look here.
Can you hear me?
Did he say something?
Yes. Can you hear? I knew it.
I hear and see everything, I am not a vegetable.
Is it true?
Is he really talking?
He is falsely accused.
Hey dumbass, you idiot.
-I hear you, moron.
-I'm sure he feels that way.
He's in the middle of the Khan scandal
and the Prime Minister
and is going to take all the blame on himself.
What is this?
Director Han's tricks?
Start treatment.
He seems crazy
but it’s unlikely that you’ll be able to pin everything on him.
What can he do? He's a loser anyway.
The best way for him is to lie here.
Are you serious now?
If they were in my place, would they lie and suffer?
Can detectives say that?
Now
I'll put my life on the line and get acupuncture.
I won't let him get away with this.
To the villain Director Khan.
Holy spirits!
I'll bite his back!
What have you forgotten here?
Queen!
-Your Majesty!
Your Majesty!
You've already eaten so much
forgetting about caution!
What are you going to snack on there?
The worst is over.
But why didn't she wake up?
The queen breathes again
but she had not yet fully come to her senses.
We have to keep an eye on her
the queen may get worse.
In other words, it's not over yet?
Tonight
everything will be decided.
The king went to Daejojong Hall.
For what?
The Queen fainted
he wants to stay by her bedside and look after her.
Fine.
It's worth changing...
I said everything is fine.
Keep your mouth shut.
Find out who, your life will be in danger.
Of course, I understand everything.
I can't believe that this girl
subordinate to the court lady Choi.
Everything is going just right.
I knew it, the spirits were on our side.
Queen Mother, are you here?
I want to perform a ritual
Here, I’m preparing for it.
It's nothing serious, so have a seat.
I want to talk to you.
I know about everything.
You asked your father to spare the queen.
That time you said
that I don't have to act alone.
-Right.
-But what
if I want to do anything?
Then
Can I surpass the queen?
I'll stay all night, you can go.
It's late, I'm afraid how you
didn't get sick either.
Everything will be fine.
You can go.
Yes.
I haven't had a single quiet day here.
The husband with whom I share the same blanket is trying to kill me.
You'll feel numb
don't hesitate and strike.
Leave?
I mustered up the courage to apologize
and this is what I get in response?
Listen, if the only person who needs an apology is
who apologizes, and not to the one who receives them,
Is this an apology?
The moment has passed. There's no point in saying anything.
I was hoping
that I will have a chance to understand you.
This is a very expensive fabric.
If I used it
I would remember it for the rest of my life.
Are you sure?
Silk was brought to you to make
silk flowers for a banquet.
Right.
And do you have any excess fabric left?
The point is
head of the kitchen
Mr. Kim Mungeun took the fabric.
Was there a similar one among that fabric?
This is...
I saw him burn something valuable
found it suspicious and took it out of the fire.
I'm sure it's her.
Prince Yeonpyeong?
Did the king have something to do with this?
What did you say?
Queen Mother and Concubine Cho
performing a ritual together within the walls of the palace?
Right.
I thought the royal concubine
have enough brains not to get involved in this,
but she seems to be just like the Queen Mother.
That's even better.
I can teach you a good lesson
these abnormal ones.
If you reprimand them for the ritual
and talismans, rumors will spread.
But they won't stop.
You're right.
I wish I could do
something more substantial.
This is the chief eunuch! I have urgent news!
Come in.
What's happened?
The queen lost her breath and was unconscious.
Lost breath?
The doctor gave her back her breath,
but she needs to be watched all night.
What happened?
It is suspected that the queen was poisoned while cooking in the kitchen.
Kim Soyeon
If you want to fight with all your heart,
if you want to overcome her with all your heart,
then from now on
You shouldn't have secrets from me.
Do you agree?
Yes, I agree.
Then tell me if it's worth it
should the king know what's going on here?
The king wishes
the same as us.
Is she breathing?
Breathing.
But if she's sleeping,
why is she so quiet?
What's happened? Are you hurt?
Why?
You always wanted a daughter
are you happy now?
You are in pain, you are suffering.
It must be even stronger now
you miss your mother.
You can handle everything.
Get well soon
to be full of strength and energy again.
You promised me to live
following the social distancing rule.
I will forgive you and your strange speech,
and cocky behavior.
Just wake up.
I'm so glad you haven't left yet.
What's happened?
The queen is in a vegetative state.
Has she stopped breathing?
Fortunately, the doctor returned it to her.
I want you to go to Seongwonjong Hall.
Someone wants to harm the queen?
We'll strike
by Queen Mother and Concubine Cho.
Go away, evil spirit!
Gods, listen to my prayers!
Cast out the evil spirit!
What are you doing?
How dare you break in here?
Don't know what this place is?
Do you think you can get away with this?
I'll ask you the same thing.
Do you think it's a threat to life?
Queens can you get away with it?
-What's happened?
-Out of the way!
-What are you doing?
-Search everything!
What a horror! What are you doing?
-Oh no!
-What horror!
I prayed for a peaceful life in the palace!
This rat was found near the Daejojeon Hall.
I have nothing to do with it.
Do you want to say that the shaman acted alone?
It seems your gods haven't told you when you'll die.
It will happen today.
Please, have mercy on me.
I was only following the Queen Mother's orders.
Shut your mouth!
I will perform a ritual that will break the curse.
A ritual that will break the curse?
You serve God, not your king!
Apparently you decided that the palace is a circus!
Everything is wrong!
Late.
The queen's life is in danger.
This cannot be true.
You performed the ritual.
And now you don’t believe in its consequences?
You have been deceived by a scammer!
Look what this has led to!
Because of you, the reputation of the entire dynasty has come to an end,
you tried to kill the queen,
and also committed a serious crime,
leaving us all confused!
How are you going to pay for your sins?
May I know the queen's condition?
Pretending like you don't know the answer?
Well, I'll tell you what happened to the queen.
She was poisoned.
Arsenic was found among the food in the kitchen.
Arsenic.
I'm sure you know what kind of poison this is.
I'm sure
you know more about her than I do.
And again you are back to your old ways.
Again you accuse me of killing the king.
People are fools who quickly forget the past.
Not knowing how valuable a life saved at the cost of the life of one’s own child is.
That time it was you
begged me.
Instead of investigating the king's death,
poisoned with arsenic,
you asked me for your life.
And what do I see?
You lured the innocent concubine Cho into your dirty rituals and tried to poison the queen!
Aren't you ashamed of the deceased king?
Although why be surprised, if you have a conscience,
you would die after him.
There is no use in apologizing.
You know more than anyone else
how much I have done wrong.
Since you think so, I have no choice.
I order
quarter the shaman and the court lady Khan!
-Yes!
Please, have mercy on me!
Let me in!
As for the Queen Mother...
Please!
Have mercy!
Please have mercy on me!
Praying won't help you this time!
How long should I turn a blind eye to your misdeeds?
This time you won't get off that easy!
I was wrong!
Please give me a chance
atone for guilt!
How are you going to atone for such a grave sin?
You must be sure
that the king
submits to you with all his soul.
You were sure that the deceased king was in your power,
therefore they resigned as regent.
Or have you forgotten?
Are the Queen Mother's words troubling you?
For your peace of mind, I will check
What kind of a man is His Majesty.
What are you doing here?
Your Majesty!
What's all the commotion?
I'm transferring the queen.
Are you transporting?
Where?
I can't tell you.
Can you tell me where you are taking the queen?
Did something happen?
A mask of lies.
The queen was cursed in Seongwonjong.
It was the Queen Mother
and Royal Concubine Cho.
Concubine Cho would never do such a thing.
Are you saying the queen's illness is due to a curse?
Arsenic was found in the royal kitchen.
Now the investigation will be conducted by the Detective Department.
In this regard, I have questions for you.
What and where did you do with Prince Yeonpyeong
the night after the royal wedding?
What do you allow yourself?
Show your real face.
Apparently your memory is failing you.
If this is the case, I will have to formally interrogate the prince.
Not a step further!
Your Majesty.
Please don't move.
Otherwise your guards will have to
disrespect and harm you.
Stop.
This is the king's order.
This is my woman.
Just touch her with your finger,
and this sword will cut your throat.
I didn't know the queen was so dear to you.
There's a lot you don't know.
Let me teach you a lesson.
Do you see me?
I am the king of this country!
Whose warriors are you?
My guard.
Move away.
Your Majesty.
Isn't this treason?
Get your people out
if you don't want to
for blood to be shed in Daejojon.
If you command, Prince Yeonpyeong
happy to get his hands dirty.
I just have questions for you.
You came on time.
I did not order the investigation to begin.
Who does the Detective Department report to now?
I'll look into the matter myself first.
And you can't blame the innocent again.
Only the queen is innocent here!
I already told you.
Make her suffer
and your life will also become torture.
I said it was not a threat.
But I have to take my words back.
How dare you!
This woman is no longer your cousin.
Her happiness
sorrows and safety are now a concern
not the head of the Detective Department - you,
and mine.
The Queen will be taken to her family's home.
Prepare the palanquin.
-Yes.
Let's leave.
I'm late.
You are so
tried to hide this side of themselves.
Watch her carefully.
Yes.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone.
Stay alert until you arrive.
And stand guard all night upon arrival.
Yes!
I bet everyone but me
will be able to breathe out in the palace.
And why does this make you feel better?
Wait, Kim Hwan should have been here by now.
And here is the devil himself.
I was already worried that we wouldn't meet
before I leave...
Who is this?
Today I found a good friend.
This is Lee Senban.
We met when I was looking for my friend Lee Senman.
We are destined to be friends.
I wanted to have a drink with you
and play cards.
Do you want a tavern here or what?
Drink and play cards? What kind of person are you?
And what? That's what we do here.
Only you can do this.
Only for you, Kim Hwan.
-Only for you.
-What?
I didn't know it was so easy to get interested in you.
Is it that easy for you to make friends?
Do you have more of them than you could possibly wish for?
Apparently I was one of your friends for the evening,
one of your many friends.
Well, did you send your friend Lee Sengbang home?
You are called to the palace.
What?
Why is no one here today?
Everyone went to see
for something interesting without me?
Feeling like everyone has abandoned me.
Lee Senman, you're alive!
Finally met!
I made a mistake, I confused you with a friend.
I'm sorry.
I'm not your friend.
But I have something interesting.
What are these things? They look strange.
This...
The curfew has not yet been lifted.
-Why are you on the street?
- Hide it.
You...
Was one spanking not enough?
Are you selling books with obscenities again?
Obscenity?
It was he who wanted to sell them to me.
You are accused of violating morality.
Take them away.
Yes.
-Wait, I...
-Let me go.
-Wait.
-You can be more gentle.
-Here is Herod.
You can be gentler, but I'm scared.
He asked specifically about the night after the wedding.
So the queen told him everything.
It seemed strange to me that she was silent for so long.
If he knew that I tried to kill her,
The matter would not have ended with just one interrogation.
On the day of his appointment, he read out the saying:
"Having saved the empire from discord,
power strikes fear into the king."
Self-confident turkey.
He threatened to take away your throne.
If he's willing to go that far,
you should have bitten your tongue.
And then
he would continue to put pressure on His Majesty.
His Majesty would have revealed himself anyway.
Smart guy.
He must have found something.
I'll find out how much he knows.
For now we can only hope
that the queen will wake up.
This is the most important thing for everyone.
What about training?
Kim Byungin is hunting our heads.
We need to put in even more effort.
There is very little time left.
God.
Raise the lantern.
How far is Her Majesty?
She's on her way here.
Are you sure she's not on the verge of death?
Yes, fortunately, everything worked out.
God.
How could this happen?
Poisoned? How could she be poisoned?
I have already called the best doctors in Joseon.
God.
Be that as it may,
you need to remain calm.
You need to calm down and think rationally.
What is it?
God.
How cruel.
The Queen Mother's husband was poisoned.
How can you blame her?
The situation is difficult
Hwajin, stay away from the Queen Mother.
This happened on the day of my visit.
I gave them an opportunity.
Don't beat yourself up over this.
They would have made their move anyway.
But
why did you move the queen back to her father's house?
She must have been lonely in the palace.
In her dream she called her mother.
But Her Majesty dreamed about it.
About what?
Is something wrong?
-No.
-Don't worry.
I will send my brother as soon as everything is decided.
Your Majesty.
I beg you.
Will you go against the will of the king?
Please don't get hurt.
Fine.
Now that you're here
It's like we've gone back in time.
Benin.
You're the only one looking for me when I run away.
I won't let you lose yourself.
And I will never forget.
If only I could go back to that day.
This is my woman.
You were supposed to be mine.
And I am yours.
Do you even know who I am?
The same Kim Hwan who is about to become an official
Detective department.
It wasn't enough what he did,
decided to bargain with your future appointment?
Bargain?
I am a righteous man.
Is it really by face and talents?
can't you see that I'm Sungkyunkwan's student?
I will not tolerate injustice...
Quiet here.
Look what a talkative guy you got.
How dare you? If you let me go immediately,
I'll give you five nyans in silver.
Or can you
give them to me?
In return, we will teach you an invaluable lesson.
As soon as you hear what I say,
you will no longer be who you were.
You will become truly mature.
-Are you going to the palace?
-Yes. Have you just returned home?
Heard what happened
between you and the king yesterday.
Yes, I understand.
Even if he doesn't look great,
If you put so much pressure on him, he will become one.
Why did he act without my order?
This is because...
His eyes.
He has the eyes of a man
hiding his aspirations.
I didn't want the Queen Dowager to worry,
So he acted rashly.
Be careful.
Father.
Did you find out how the queen is doing?
I heard the crisis is over.
She hasn't come to her senses yet.
But he'll get better soon.
Anything else you want to say?
I heard the dowager queen
mentioned the deposition of the queen.
She said this in a fit of anger.
She doesn't really want this.
You have nothing to worry about.
I know very well how much you care for the queen.
Maybe not as much as you
but I take good care of her too, so don't worry.
Yes.
See you at the palace.
The queen's father sent gifts again.
How is the queen?
The crisis is over
but she needs rest for now,
so she returned home.
She is constantly sick.
She never recovered from that incident.
What should I call it?
It's like she's broken.
I'm trying to let her get stronger
but suddenly she becomes a vegetable.
She's too weak.
What if Concubine Cho gives birth to a prince first?
Then the Queen Mother will rebel again.
Don't worry.
I have prepared a backup plan.
Backup plan?
I made sure that the other two
who we considered for the role of queen,
so they didn’t marry anyone.
You are a reliable brother.
I heard that yesterday Benin accused the king.
Yesterday everyone behaved strangely towards the king.
It's as if the king is hiding something.
This king is different from the deceased one.
That's how it should be. You chose it yourself.
I elevated the king to his place for only one reason.
So that you don't have to make painful decisions,
as it was under the late king.
And it's true.
It was quite painful.
I defended the country at the cost of my grandson's blood
in my arms.
And if anyone dares to destroy it,
he will not be forgiven.
Detective department.
-First you have to.
-No, you first.
No, you first.
Where am I?
In Joseon or Korea?
In Joseon.
I can't say I'm glad because I lost them
but I can’t say that I’m sad, because I’m glad that I can check it out.
Why does everything sparkle so much here?
Gold of the Empire.
Incas?
Your Majesty!
It seemed to me that I was in some other place.
You've finally woken up!
It's like deja vu.
Just let's not make any fuss.
But you almost died.
They even stopped breathing completely.
Don't cry.
Stopped breathing?
According to the royal physician,
you were without a vegetable.
As if you had died.
So, here too.
But where am I?
You are home.
So,
I can't avoid meeting
someone you shouldn't date.
-What?
- So, no difficulties,
but there is someone here with whom I don’t feel at ease.
The one who is essentially my real enemy -
the woman's father.
Your Majesty.
-This is happiness, queen.
-God.
Your Majesty, are you okay? Can you breathe?
What do you want? Should I call the royal physician?
It looks like you're about to lose consciousness.
Here, drink.
Fine.
These are herbs for restoring yin energy.
Excellent.
Why are you so sweaty?
Holy heavens.
I was so worried.
I didn't sleep last night.
I completely lost my appetite
and I haven’t eaten anything for two days.
Every time I get up I feel dizzy.
-You must be deeply shocked.
-Yes.
The root of disease is worries and troubles,
you need to rest and calm down.
Yes, of course, I will do that.
Hope you feel better soon. It's time for me to go.
Your Majesty.
Where are you going?
Holy saints.
I can't do this. I have to show respect.
Your Majesty.
That's it. What are you doing? You're embarrassing me.
No, no, I don’t dare.
Please accept my bow, Your Majesty.
No!
Look, you.
How so?
Let me bow to you once again.
Father.
Being a queen in Joseon is so uncomfortable.
Let me while I'm here
to just be your daughter Soyeon.
The higher the position, the greater the loneliness.
Okay, I understand.
While you're here
I'll do it this way
as you wish.
Okay, now sit down.
Fine. Thank you.
Be careful.
No matter how you decorate the room,
it still seemed empty.
But as soon as you returned, the room began to shine.
Yes.
The room is so bright that it blinds your eyes.
I like.
Don't worry, nothing will tarnish your reputation.
I took care of everything.
I have prepared all the best.
Next one, come on in.
I didn't see a single doctor there,
and there's a whole crowd here?
Is anyone else due to come?
-Some kind of holiday?
-This is breakfast.
To restore strength
your father made you turtle soup.
Here.
Turtles in the morning?
Be careful.
Why? What's there?
It's such an honor to serve you, Your Majesty.
She is the best beauty artist in Joseon.
I'm naturally beautiful. I don't need her help.
Come on in.
Call for overthrow and poisoning.
They are doing everything to get rid of Her Majesty.
Don't worry.
No matter how hard they try
harm Her Majesty,
I will increase my power.
With a brother like you, she has nothing to worry about.
Are you familiar with this material?
This is regular silk.
Is there something wrong with him?
Have you given someone clothes made from this material?
After Her Majesty became Queen,
I only received gifts, I didn’t give them myself.
The only person I offer gifts to is the Queen Dowager.
It's clear.
But you know...
Recently my warehouse has been robbed twice.
This silk could be there.
Was your home attacked?
No no.
It is dangerous to keep all your valuables in one place.
It is better to place them in different places.
I have several warehouses.
But the robbers chose only those with the most valuable things.
Just thinking about it, my neck immediately goes numb.
My beloved treasures.
Is it possible to find out among the stolen
was this silk or not?
Too much has been stolen.
And keeping records of valuable property was dangerous.
By the way...
Don't tell anyone about the warehouses.
It's not good if people find out about this.
I understand.
But have you heard anything strange from your father?
Did something happen?
This whole situation with Her Majesty: saved the king with his concubine
and ruined her relationship with the Queen Dowager - worries me.
I have nightmares in which she is overthrown.
Overthrown? Why are you thinking about this?
There are rumors that one of the queen contenders
delivered a secret message.
Is it possible that they want to choose a new queen?
I'm so worried that I've been overeating these days.
They will not give up on Her Majesty.
Is it true?
I have to try and send
more gifts for the Queen Dowager.
How are you feeling?
What?
This is nothing. I'll be there soon...
No, maybe not so fast.
How could this happen?
I completely forgot that I was no longer young and was careless.
I don't have time for fun.
How are you feeling?
I look like a doll.
Wonderful!
Do you like it?
This book is already overgrown with mold.
Terrible stench.
If you were a man
would enter the palace after passing the state exam.
You really enjoyed studying.
Who liked to study it?
I tried only for my father.
Mom died giving me life.
And I decided that I had to pay back for this.
Apparently that's why you even at night
We studied hard on our birthday.
Soyeon.
Happy birthday.
Because on my birthday we remembered my mother,
I never smiled.
What was that now?
Your Majesty.
Your memories come back!
What? What are these memories that seem to be mine, but not really?
Kim Changhyuk
Out of the way! Go away!
Kim Chang-hyuk, current Minister of War.
Together with a group of military men he collected
excessively high war tax.
Kim Seok-keun, current left-wing councilor.
Responsible for finances
through the grain exchange
appropriates royal gifts.
Kim Byung-hak, current State Councilor.
Tax criminal:
conspired with local governors
and imposed taxes on empty lands.
Kim Mungeun.
Queen's father.
This is what I'm talking about.
Queen's father
head of the royal guard.
Famous manufacturer
dealing with everything from rice loans to the war tax system.
Kim Jwageun.
Acting troop commander.
At the peak of its power,
the one who founded this entire corrupt system.
Secret
Everyone in the palace has a secret.
A secret hidden by lies.
A secret that cannot be seen or heard.
A secret waiting for the right moment.
To keep a secret deep in your heart,
Initial Instruction for Children
we all wear masks.
Cho Hwajin
But the secret
will definitely open up.
Your Majesty, your memories have returned!
Everything is confused. Go away, woman, go away!
Why do you keep getting weirder and weirder over time?
There is something I haven't told anyone about.
-Help.
-That smell of dampness.
Recently, many warehouses have been robbed in the capital.
-And what?
-I'm interested
maybe this is how you make money.
Today we will clear everything up.
This is what I was waiting for.